{
    "subject": "resource/Fraunces_Tavern",
    "predicate": "property/owner",
    "object": "Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York, Inc.",
    "human_readable": "The owner of Fraunces Tavern is Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York, Inc.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.920363187789917,
            "question": "Who owns Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8541874885559082,
            "question": "What state is the organization that owns Fraunces Tavern located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8114230036735535,
            "question": "What is the full name of the organization that owns Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7688159942626953,
            "question": "What type of organization owns Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6936551928520203,
            "question": "Is Fraunces Tavern owned by a private individual or an organization?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6708618998527527,
            "question": "Can you name other historic landmarks owned by organizations similar to the one that owns Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5926539301872253,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.521169126033783,
            "question": "What are some events or activities that might take place at Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4300430119037628,
            "question": "Do you know any famous people who have visited or dined at Fraunces Tavern?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32845520973205566,
            "question": "Why is it important to preserve historical sites like Fraunces Tavern?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The owner of Fraunces Tavern is Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York, Inc.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2707_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Do you know any famous people who have visited or dined at Fraunces Tavern?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2707_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some events or activities that might take place at Fraunces Tavern?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2707_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the historical significance of Fraunces Tavern?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2707_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2707_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON format with the value as \"yes\" or \"no\":\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents support the triple that the owner of Fraunces Tavern is Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York, Inc. (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2707/re-ranker-msmarco/38.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2707/re-ranker-msmarco/60.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Fraunces Tavern has been owned since 1904 by Sons of the Revolution in the State of New York Inc.\" This supports the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}